A Guide to the Adèle Goodman Clark papers, 1849-1978
Virginia Commonwealth University, James Branch Cabell Library
- Series II: Business/Civic Organization Correspondence, undated, 1903-1971
  - Subseries C: Alice Dooley/Josephine and Nora Houston, undated, 1915-1953
    - Young Woman's Literary Club, 1914-1915 (Box 38)
- Series III: Equal Suffrage League of Virginia, undated, 1892-1926
  - Subseries A: President/Secretary Correspondence, undated, 1909-1920
    - Fragile materials (Box 39)
    - 1909 (Box 40)
    - January - July 1910 (Box 40)
    - August - December 1910 (Box 40)
    - 1911 (Box 40)
    - 1912 (Box 40)
    - January - March 1913 (Box 40)
    - April - May 1913 (Box 40)
    - June 1913 (Box 40)
    - July 19 August 1913 (Box 40)
    - September 1913 (Box 41)
    - October 1913 (Box 41)
    - November 1913 (Box 41)
    - December 1913 (Box 41)
    - January 1914 (Box 41)
    - February 1914 (Box 41)
    - March - August 1914 (Box 41)
    - September - December 1914 (Box 42)
    - January - June 1915 (Box 42)
    - July - October 1915 (Box 42)
    - November - December 1915 (Box 42)
    - January - March 1916 (Box 42)
    - April 1916 (Box 42)
    - May 1916 (Box 42)
    - June 1916 (Box 42)
    - July 1916 (Box 42)
    - August 1916 (Box 42)
    - September 1916 (Box 43)
    - October 1916 (Box 43)
    - November 1916 (Box 43)
    - December 1916 (Box 43)
    - January - February 1917 (Box 43)
    - March 1917 (Box 43)
    - April 1917 (Box 43)
    - May 1917 (Box 43)
    - June 1917 (Box 43)
    - July - August 1917 (Box 43)
    - September - October 1917 (Box 43)
    - November 1917 (Box 43)
    - December 1917 (Box 44)
    - January 1918 (Box 44)
    - February 1918 (Box 44)
    - March 1918 (Box 44)
    - April 1918 (Box 44)
    - May 1918 (Box 44)
    - June 1918 (Box 44)
    - July 1918 (Box 44)
    - August 1918 (Box 44)
    - September 1918 (Box 44)
    - October 1918 (Box 44)
    - November 1918 (Box 44)
    - December 1918 (Box 44)
    - January 1919 (Box 45)
    - February 1919 (Box 45)
    - March 1919 (Box 45)
    - April 1919 (Box 45)
    - May 1919 (Box 45)
    - June 1919 (Box 45)
    - July 1-15, 1919 (Box 45)
    - July 16-31, 1919 (Box 45)
    - August 1-15, 1919 (Box 45)
    - August 16-32, 1919 (Box 45)
    - September 1-15, 1919 (Box 45)
    - September 16-30, 1919 (Box 46)
    - October 1-15, 1919 (Box 46)
    - October 16-31, 1919 (Box 46)
    - November 1-15, 1919 (Box 46)
    - November 16-30, 1919 (Box 46)
    - December 1-15, 1919 (Box 46)
    - December 16-31, 1919 (Box 46)
    - January 1-15, 1920 (Box 46)
    - January 16-31, 1920 (Box 46)
    - February 1920 (Box 46)
    - March 1920 (Box 46)
    - April 1920 (Box 46)
    - May 1920 (Box 47)
    - June 1920 (Box 47)
    - July 1920 (Box 47)
    - August 1920 (Box 47)
    - September 1-15, 1920 (Box 47)
    - September 16 - September 30, 1920 (Box 47)
    - October 1920 (Box 47)
    - November - December 1920 (Box 48)
    - Undated Material (1 of 2) (Box 48)
    - Undated Material (2 of 2) (Box 48)
  - Subseries B: Equal Suffrage League of Richmond, undated, 1915-1920
    - Bulletins and Circulars, 1919-1920 (Box 48)
    - Clay Ward Pledge Lists and Maps, undated (Box 48)
    - Correspondence [Edith Clark Cowles], 1915-1918 (Box 48)
    - Essay Contest, undated (Box 48)
    - Executive Council--Declaration of Principles, Resolutions, Information Brief (Box 48)
    - Membership List, undated (Box 48)
    - Minutes, 1915, 1920 (Box 48)
    - Officer List, undated (Box 48)
    - Recording Secretary Notebook, 1919 (Box 48)
  - Subseries C: National American Women Suffrage Association, undated, 1913-1920
    - Americanization Committee--Bulletins and Memoranda, 1917 (Box 48)
    - Announcements, Bulletins, Convention Brochures, Miscellaneous, undated (Box 48)
    - Convention Report, undated (Box 48)
    - Flyers and Handbills, undated (Box 49)
    - Handbook and Proceedings of Jubilee Convention, 1919 (Box 49)
    - Headquarters Newsletter, 1916-1917 (Box 49)
    - National Congressional Committee Special Bulletin, 1916 (Box 49)
    - National Suffrage News, 1917 (Box 49)
    - Pamphlets [Includes "Efficiency Booklet Series" pamphlets], undated (Box 49)
    - Political Equality Leaflets, undated (Box 49)
    - Presidential Address, 1919 (Box 49)
    - Press Releases, undated, 1917-1920 (Box 49)
    - Questionnaire, undated (Box 49)
    - Shaw Memorial [Anna Howard Shaw], 1919-1920 (Box 49)
    - Study Outline Series--Women Suffrage: A Study Outline, undated (Box 49)
    - Suffrage Literature Lists, undated (Box 49)
    - Suffrage Pageant and Parade, 1913 (Box 49)
    - Victory Convention, Condensed Minutes and Handbook of NAWSA, 1920 (Box 49)
  - Subseries D: Other Suffrage Organizations, undated, 1910-1926
    - Alabama Equal Suffrage Association, undated (Box 50)
    - Boston Equal Suffrage Association for Good Government, undated (Box 50)
    - Brooklyn Woman Suffrage Association, 1911 (Box 50)
    - Chicago Men's Equal Suffrage League, undated (Box 50)
    - Council of National Defense--Woman's Committee, undated (Box 50)
    - Empire State Campaign Committee, 1914-1915 (Box 50)
    - Equal Suffrage League [Virginia League of Women Voters]--Citizenship Committee, 1920 (Box 50)
    - Equal Suffrage League--Custodial Committee, 1926 (Box 50)
    - Equal Suffrage Association of North Carolina, undated (Box 50)
    - Farmers' Educational and Co-Operative Union of America [Virginia Division], 1911 (Box 50)
    - International Woman Suffrage Alliance, 1924-1926 (Box 50)
    - Iowa Equal Suffrage Association, 1910-1917 (Box 50)
    - Just Government League of Maryland, 1913-1921 (Box 50)
    - Kentucky Equal Rights Association, undated (Box 50)
    - League of Woman Voters--Program, undated (Box 50)
    - National College Equal Suffrage League, undated (Box 50)
    - National Committee for Suffrage Agriculture, undated (Box 50)
    - National Council of Women--Biennial Report, 1916 (Box 50)
    - National Tax Association, 1919 (Box 50)
    - National Union of Women Citizens--Constitution, 1919 (Box 50)
    - National War Savings Committee, 1917 (Box 50)
    - National Woman Suffrage Publishing Company, undated (Box 50)
    - National Woman's Christian Temperance Union, 1917 (Box 50)
    - New Jersey Men's League for Woman Suffrage, undated (Box 50)
    - New York State Woman Suffrage Party, undated, 1916-1917 (Box 50)
    - North Western Federation of Colored Women's Clubs, 1920 (Box 50)
    - Pennsylvania Woman Suffrage Association, undated, 1915 (Box 50)
    - Public Instruction, Department of, 1912 (Box 50)
    - Richmond Equal Rights Association, undated (Box 50)
    - St. Louis Equal Suffrage League, undated (Box 50)
    - Southern States Woman Suffrage Conference, undated, 1915 (Box 50)
    - State Fair Committee, 1912 (Box 50)
    - Tennessee State Fair--Woman's Department, 1912 (Box 50)
    - Unites States Department of Labor--Information and Education Service, 1919 (Box 50)
    - Virginia Association Opposed to Woman Suffrage, undated (Box 50)
    - Virginia Central Citizenship Committee, 1920 (Box 50)
    - Virginia Federation of Labor, undated, 1912, 1917 (Box 50)
    - Virginia Good Roads Association, 1920 (Box 51)
    - Virginia State Central Democratic Committee, 1920 (Box 51)
    - Virginia State Federation of Woman's Clubs, 1912-1919 (Box 51)
    - Virginia State War Council, undated (Box 51)
    - War Loan Organization--Woman's Division, 1919 (Box 51)
    - West Virginia Equal Suffrage Association, undated (Box 51)
    - Wisconsin Woman Suffrage Association, 1917 (Box 51)
    - Woman's Christian Temperance Union/Woman's Temperance League, 1911-1916 (Box 51)
    - Woman's Land Army of America "Women on the Land" February, 1918 (Box 51)
    - Woman's War Service--Registration Bureau, undated (Box 51)
  - Subseries E: Topical File, undated, 1892-1920
    - Annual Address--Lila Meade Valentine, 1911 (Box 51)
    - Annual Reports, undated (Box 51)
    - Anti-Suffrage Literature, undated (Box 51)
    - Anti-Suffrage Literature-- Woman Patriot, 1919-1920 (Box 51)
    - Appointment Calendar, 1916 (Box 51)
    - Audit Statement, undated (Box 51)
    - Ballots, 1918 (Box 51)
    - Biographies--Suffrage Women, undated (Box 51)
    - Booklist, 1916 (Box 51)
    - Branch Minutes and Reports, undated (Box 51)
    - Briefs [on Federal Suffrage Amendment], undated, 1919 (Box 51)
    - Budgetary Material, undated (Box 51)
    - Budgetary Material--Pledge and Donations Lists, undated (Box 51)
    - Bulletins and Circulars, 1911-1917 (Box 51)
    - Bulletins and Circulars, undated, 1918-1920 (Box 51)
    - Business and Professional Woman, 1920 (Box 52)
    - Citizenship/Political Education School Material, undated, 1920 (Box 52)
    - City Ordinances, 1917 (Box 52)
    - Club List, undated (Box 52)
    - Conference Brochures, 1913 (Box 52)
    - Convention--Delegate Lists, 1919-1922 (Box 52)
    - Convention Minutes, 1920 (Box 52)
    - Convention (Box 52)
      - Notes, undated (Box 52)
      - Programs, 1916 (Box 52)
      - Resolutions, 1913-1920 (Box 52)
    - Correspondence--Executive and Headquarters Secretary Reports, undated, 1914-1919 (Box 52)
    - Democratic Convention--State, Roanoke, 1916, 1920 (Box 52)
    - Dollar Post-Card Plan, undated (Box 52)
    - Draft Speeches--Lila Meade Valentine, undated (Box 52)
    - Essay (Box 52)
      - Bosher, Kate Langley "Legislature's Chance," undated (Box 52)
      - Bowne, B.P. "Man's View of Woman Suffrage," undated (Box 52)
      - Clark, Adèle "Symbol of Civilization," undated (Box 52)
      - Clarke, Mary Pollard "Human Rights--Not in Violation of State's Rights," undated (Box 52)
      - Dahl, E. Peabody "Suffrage, A Woman's Right and Duty" March 11, 1920 (Box 52)
      - Foster, Mrs. W.W. "Anti-Suffrage Home," undadted (Box 52)
      - Foster, Mrs. W.W. "Woman's Work," undated (Box 52)
      - Henning, Julia R., undated, 1910 (Box 52)
      - Mason, Lucy R. "Divine Discontent" [Lucy Cary?], undated (Box 52)
      - Mason, Lucy R. "Expediency or Right?," 1913 (Box 52)
      - Mason, Lucy R. "Religious and Social Aspect of the Suffrage Movement," undated (Box 52)
      - Norris, Kathleen "Forty-Five and Comfortable and Nothing to Do," undated (Box 52)
      - Temple, Alice "Plea for Equal Suffrage," undated (Box 52)
      - Winn, M.D. "Women's Votes Make Better Babies," undated (Box 52)
    - Essay Drafts, undated (Box 52)
    - Executive Committee Plan, 1920 (Box 52)
    - "Facts and Fallacies" by Adèle Clark, 1912 (Box 52)
    - Flyers and Handbills, undated, 1913, 1919-1920 (Box 52)
    - Ginter Park Election, 1912 (Box 52)
    - International Suffrage Literature, undated, 1911 (Box 52)
    - Itineraries, undated (Box 52)
    - Labor [includes Commissioner of Labor (James B. Doherty) paper], 1912 (Box 52)
    - Leaflets, undated (Box 52)
    - Lee [Robert E.] Camp, 1892 (Box 52)
    - Legislative Material, undated, 1917-1920 (Box 53)
    - Letters to the Editor, undated, 1913-1920 (Box 53)
    - Liberty Loan Campaign, undated, 1918-1919 (Box 53)
    - Lists--Miscellaneous, undated (Box 53)
    - Membership Cards and Lists (1 of 2) (Box 53)
    - Membership Cards and Lists (2 of 2) (Box 53)
    - Membership/Officer Lists (Bound Volumes) (Box 53)
    - Minutes--Board of Directors, Executive Committee, undated, 1912-1920 (Box 53)
    - Monthly Demonstrations, 1917 (Box 53)
    - National Convention Speech--Mrs. Lila Mead Valentine September, 1916 (Box 53)
    - National Woman Suffrage Convention Delegates List, 1919 (Box 53)
    - Newspaper Clippings, undated (Box 54)
    - Newspaper Clippings, undated (Box 54)
    - Newspaper Clippings [photocopied], undated 1914-1920 (Box 54)
    - Notebook--Adèle Clark, undated (Box 54)
    - Notebook--Edith Clark Cowles, 1919-1920 (Box 54)
    - Notebook--Nora Houston, undated (Box 54)
    - Notebook--Ida Mae Thompson, 1909(?)-1920 (Box 54)
    - Organizational Charts and History, undated (Box 54)
    - Organization Plan, 1917 (Box 54)
    - Patriotic Luncheons, undated (Box 54)
    - Presidential Campaign Flyers--19th Century (Box 54)
    - Press Bureau--Correspondence/Suffrage Data, 1915-1916 (Box 54)
    - Public Meetings Permit, 1915 (Box 54)
    - Red Cross Auxiliary War Work Reports, 1917 (Box 54)
    - Resolutions, undated (Box 54)
    - Social Hygiene--Pamphlets (Box 54)
    - Souvenir Program "Jollies of 1919," 1919 (Box 54)
    - Stanton [Elizabeth Cady] Centennial Luncheon, 1915 (Box 55)
    - State Suffrage Association Director, 1914 (Box 55)
    - State Suffrage Association List, undated (Box 55)
    - Suffrage (Box 55)
      - Addresses/Speeches (Box 55)
      - Clark, [Chief Justice] Walter "Ballots for Both," 1916 (Box 55)
      - Clark, Adèle (Box 55)
      - Calendars, 1914, 1917 (Box 55)
      - Diary and Handbook, 1918 (Box 55)
      - Literature Mailing List, undated (Box 55)
      - Pattern Advertisements, undated (Box 55)
      - Plays, undated, 1913-1914 (Box 55)
      - Plays--"Gaslight" scripts, undated (Box 55)
      - Poetry, undated (Box 55)
      - Post Cards, undated (Box 55)
      - Schools, undated, 1913 (Box 55)
      - Schools--Lecture Material, 1917 (Box 55)
      - Schools--Lesson Book, undated (Box 55)
      - Sketch [by Nora Houston], undated (Box 55)
    - Supplemental Literature, undated, 1919-1920 (Box 55)
    - Taylor [Alice O.] Story--"Dilsey," undated (Box 55)
    - Townsend [C.E.]--notes on League of Women Voters Chicago Convention, 1920 (Box 55)
    - Victory Loan Memo Book, 1919 (Box 56)
    - Virginia Addenda, undated (Box 56)
    - Virginia General Assembly (Box 56)
      - House of Delegates--Suffrage Position Data [arranged alphabetically by delegates last name] (Box 56)
      - Senate--Suffrage Position Data [arranged by Senate district] (Box 56)
    - Virginia Newspaper List, 1917, 1919 (Box 56)
    - Virginia Suffrage News, 1914 (Box 56)
    - Virginia Suffrage News Correspondents, Petition Blanks and Subscription Lists, 1914 (Box 56)
    - Virginia Tours (Organizing Suffrage Chapters)--Faith W. Morgan, undated (Box 56)
    - Virginia Tours (Organizing Suffrage Chapters)--Eudora W. Ramsay, undated, 1917 (Box 56)
    - Voter Registration and Election Law Materials, undated, 1920 (Box 56)
    - Woman's Bible (Box 56)
    - Woman's Journal and Suffrage News, 1912-1913, 1916 (Box 56)
    - Woman's Magazine, 1909 (Box 56)
    - World Convention Dates (Box 56)
    - Yearbooks, 1910, 1916 (Box 56)
    - Cash Book--"Your Girl and Mine," 1912 (Box 57 (Oversize))
    - Corresponding Secretary Account Book, 1910-1920 (Box 57 (Oversize))
    - Honor Roll List, undated (Box 57 (Oversize))
    - International Woman Suffrage Alliance-- International Woman Suffrage News[Damaged and Fragile Material] (Box 57 (Oversize))
    - Leslie Woman Suffrage Commission, undated (Box 57 (Oversize))
    - Lists of Names, undated (Box 57 (Oversize))
    - Membership Application Cards [on newsprint] undated (Box 57 (Oversize))
    - Minutes--Executive Board Equal Suffrage League of Richmond, 1914-1919 (Box 57 (Oversize))
    - National American Woman Suffrage Association--Bulletins, 1918 (Box 58 (Oversize))
    - National American Woman Suffrage Association--Bulletins, 1919-1920 (Box 58 (Oversize))
    - Order Book, undated (Box 58 (Oversize))
    - Subscription book (Box 58 (Oversize))
    - Suffrage Play--Title and Date unknown (Box 58 (Oversize))
    - Virginia Women's Council of Legislative Chairmen of State Organizations--Bulletins, undated, 1924-1928 (Box 58 (Oversize))
  - Subseries F: Enrollment Cards, undated, 1914-1915
    - Enrollment Cards (Box 59)
    - Enrollment Cards (Box 60)
  - Subseries G: Petitions of Equal Suffrage League, undated
    - Accomack County (Box 61)
    - Albemarle County (Box 61)
    - Alexandria County (Box 61)
    - Alleghany County (Box 61)
    - Amelia County (Box 61)
    - Amherst County (Box 61)
    - Appomattox County (Box 61)
    - Augusta County (Box 61)
    - Bedford County (Box 61)
    - Botetourt County (Box 61)
    - Brunswick County (Box 61)
    - Campbell County (Box 61)
    - Chesterfield County (Box 61)
    - Clarke County (Box 61)
    - Craig County (Box 61)
    - Culpeper County (Box 61)
    - Dinwiddie County (Box 61)
    - Elizabeth City County (Box 61)
    - Essex County (Box 61)
    - Fairfax County (Box 61)
    - Fauquier County (Box 61)
    - Frederick County (Box 61)
    - Goochland County (Box 61)
    - Grayson County (Box 61)
    - Gloucester County (Box 61)
    - Hanover County (Box 61)
    - Henrico County (Box 61)
    - Isle of Wright County (Box 61)
    - James City County (Box 61)
    - King and Queen County (Box 61)
    - King William County (Box 61)
    - Lancaster County (Box 61)
    - Loudoun County (Box 61)
    - Mecklenburg County (Box 61)
    - Miscellaneous (1 of 2) (Box 61)
    - Miscellaneous (2 of 2) (Box 61)
    - Norfolk (Box 61)
    - Northampton County (Box 61)
    - Nottoway County (Box 61)
    - Orange County (Box 62)
    - Page County (Box 62)
    - Pittsylvania County (Box 62)
    - Prince Edward County (Box 62)
    - Powhatan County (Box 62)
    - Prince William County (Box 62)
    - Princess Anne County (Box 62)
    - Richmond County (Box 62)
    - Roanoke City (Box 62)
    - Roanoke County (Box 62)
    - Rappahannock County (Box 62)
    - Rockbridge County, Local Officers (Box 62)
    - Rockingham County (Box 62)
    - Shenandoah County (Box 62)
    - Southampton County (Box 62)
    - Spottsylvania County (Box 62)
    - Suffolk (Box 62)
    - Teachers' Convention--Miscellaneous, Petitions (Box 62)
    - Warren County (Box 62)
    - Warwick County (Box 62)
  - Subseries H: General Assembly Petitions, undated (organized by both county and city)
    - Buckingham, Fredericksburg, Mecklenburg, Middlesex, Nelson, Rappahannock, Culpeper, Madison, Orange, Campbell (Box 63)
    - Chesterfield County (Box 63)
    - Henrico County, King William Co., Southampton Co. (Box 63)
    - James City, Williamsburg, Amherst, Winchester [Men], Albemarle, Frederick, Petersburg, Dinwiddie, Caroline, Norfolk, Portsmouth, Rockbridge, Bedford (Box 63)
    - Northumberland, Pulaski, Alexandria, Fairfax, Charlotte, Albemarle, Campbell (Box 63)
    - Richmond (1 of 2) (Box 63)
    - Richmond (2 of 2) (Box 63)
    - Tidewater and Miscellaneous (Box 63)
    - Miscellaneous (1 of 2) (Box 63)
    - Miscellaneous (2 of 2) (Box 63)
- Series IV: Richmond League of Women Voters, 1920-1978
  - Annual Meeting Report 1937 (Box 64)
  - Annual Reports, 1922, 1956-1957, 1967-1968 (Box 64)
  - Ballots, undated, 1931 (Box 64)
  - Board of Directors--Memoranda, Minutes, 1921, 1943-1947, 1964 (Box 64)
  - Budget Proposals and Reports [Treasurer's Report], 1928-1929, 1931-1964 (Box 64)
  - Bulletins and Circular, 1920-1929 (Box 64)
  - Bulletins and Circular, undated, 1931-1971 (Box 64)
  - Bulletins-- Time for Action! 1960-1965 (Box 64)
  - By-Laws, undated, 1953-1954, 1971 (Box 64)
  - Calendar of Events, undated 1954-1955 (Box 64)
  - Child Welfare Committee [Correspondence--Mrs. Lee, Chair], 1933 (Box 64)
  - City Council Candidate Lists, undated, 1925, 1930 (Box 64)
  - City Council Candidate Questionnaire Replies, 1932-1966 (Box 64)
  - City Democratic Committee [Richmond], 1920, 1925-1926, 1930 (Box 64)
  - City Planning Commission [Richmond], 1934-1935, 1951 (Box 64)
  - Congressional Candidates Questionnaires, 1958 (Box 65)
  - Correspondence (Box 65)
    - Efficiency in Government, Committee on, 1933 (Box 65)
    - Information Bureau, 1925 (Box 65)
    - President/Executive Secretary (Box 65)
      - 1921-1929 (Box 65)
      - 1930 - 1978 (Box 65)
  - "Dancing Feet of 1933" Program--Advertising lists, Correspondence, 1933 (Box 65)
  - Donor Lists, undated (Box 65)
  - Executive Secretary Report, 1922 (Box 65)
  - Finance Committee, 1949 (Box 65)
  - Handbills and Leaflets, undated, 1929 (Box 65)
  - Inter-racial Relations Committee--Minutes, 1948 (Box 65)
  - "Interest Finder," undated (Box 65)
  - Interest Sheet, undated (Box 65)
  - Luncheon Lists, undated (Box 65)
  - Member's Handbooks, undated, 1959 (Box 65)
  - Membership Lists, undated, 1926, 1930, 1966 (Box 65)
  - Membership Pledges and Quotas, undated (Box 65)
  - Memoranda--Adèle Clark, 1968 (Box 65)
  - News Bulletins, 1926-1930 (Box 65)
  - Newsletters (Box 65)
    - 1942-1954 (Box 65)
  - Newsletters (Box 66)
    - 1955-1959 (Box 66)
    - 1960-1963 (Box 66)
    - 1964-1968 (Box 66)
    - 1969-1971 (Box 66)
  - Newspaper Clippings regarding Richmond League of Women Voters, undated, 1931, 1966 (Box 66)
  - Newspaper Editorials, 1956 (Box 66)
  - Notes and Draft Correspondence, undated (Box 66)
  - Notes on LWV programs [Adèle Clark], 1966 (Box 66)
  - Officer Lists, 1928-1966 (Box 66)
  - Organizational History, undated, 1932-1933 (Box 66)
  - Program Agendas, undated, 1931-1932 (Box 66)
  - Programs of Legislation [Proposed], undated, 1935-1936 (Box 66)
  - Programs of Study and Work [Proposed] undated, 1930-1931 (Box 66)
  - Questionnaire, undated (Box 66)
  - Reports--State League President, undated, 1929-1932 (Box 66)
  - Republican Club of Richmond, VA, 1921 (Box 66)
  - Resolutions, undated, 1920-1921 (Box 67)
  - Richmond Child Labor Committee, 1947 (Box 67)
  - Richmond City Planning Board--Report, 1939 (Box 67)
  - Richmond City (Box 67)
    - Proposed Annexation Report, 1936 (Box 67)
    - Public Utilities, Department of--Annual Reports, 1929, 1943 (Box 67)
    - Public Welfare, Department of (Box 67)
      - Annual Reports, 1927, 1935/Illegitimacy Study, 1910-1955 (Box 67)
      - Reports to Its Citizens, 1956 (Box 67)
      - Survey of Affairs Report, 1935 (Box 67)
  - Richmond Council on Adult Education, 1935-1936 (Box 67)
  - Richmond Public Library, 1922 (Box 67)
  - Richmond Woman's Organizations Lists, 1920-1924 (Box 67)
  - Round Table--The Industrial South, 1931 (Box 67)
  - Special Committee of Review--Minutes, undated (Box 67)
  - State Fiscal Policy Committee, 1963 (Box 67)
  - Virginia Cookery Book Memoranda [A. Clark], 1954 (see also: Series V, Subseries J) (Box 67)
  - Virginia General Assembly Candidates Questionnaires, 1947, 1965 (Box 67)
  - Voters Service Committee--City Council Candidates Report, 1948 (Box 67)
  - Ward Meetings--Minutes, 1921 (Box 67)
  - Yearbooks, 1949-1950, 1954-1955 (Box 67)
  - Y.W.C.A. Luncheon--Correspondence and Lists, 1934 (Box 67)
- Series V: Virginia League of Women Voters, undated, 1915-1967
  - Subseries A: President/Executive Secretary Correspondence, undated, 1920-1944
    - November - December, 1920 (Box 67)
    - January, 1921 (Box 67)
    - February, 1921 (Box 68)
    - March - April, 1921 (Box 68)
    - May - June, 1921 (Box 68)
    - July, 1921 (Box 68)
    - August, 1921 (Box 68)
    - September - October, 1921 (Box 68)
    - November, 1921 (Box 68)
    - December, 1921 (Box 68)
    - January - March, 1922 (Box 68)
    - April - June, 1922 (Box 69)
    - July - September, 1922 (Box 69)
    - October - December, 1922 (Box 69)
    - January, 1923 (Box 69)
    - February - March, 1923 (Box 69)
    - April - June, 1923 (Box 69)
    - July - September, 1923 (Box 69)
    - October, 1923 (Box 70)
    - November - December, 1923 (Box 70)
    - January - February, 1924 (Box 70)
    - March, 1924 (Box 70)
    - April, 1924 (Box 70)
    - May - June, 1924 (Box 70)
    - July - August, 1924 (Box 70)
    - September, 1924 (Box 70)
    - October, 1924 (Box 71)
    - November - December, 1924 (Box 71)
    - January, 1925 (Box 71)
    - February, 1925 (Box 71)
    - March, 1925 (Box 71)
    - April, 1925 (Box 71)
    - May, 1925 (Box 71)
    - June, 1925 (Box 71)
    - July - September, 1925 (Box 71)
    - October - December, 1925 (Box 72)
    - January - March, 1926 (Box 72)
    - April, 1926 (Box 72)
    - May - June, 1926 (Box 72)
    - July - August, 1926 (Box 72)
    - September, 1926 (Box 72)
    - October - December, 1926 (Box 72)